Guide to the Vassar College Biographical Files, 1872-2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- R
  - Reissman, Frank, Jr.
  - Riggs, Austen
  - Riley, Woodbridge
  - Ritter, Frederick Louis
  - Ritterskamp, James J., Jr., [4 folders]
  - Riviello, Tonia C.
  - Robbins, Mary Ann
  - Robbins, Susannah
  - Roberts, Edith A., [2 folders]
  - Roberts, Nancy Girling (Mrs. William A.)
  - Robinson, Ezekiel Gilman (trustee)
  - Robinson, Kenneth M.
  - Robinson, Ruth W.
  - Robinson, Stuart
  - Robinson, Thomas
  - Robinson, Winifred
  - Robischon, Thomas
  - Roche, Josephine
  - Rock, Elizabeth J.
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette (Hooker) (trustee)
  - Rockefeller, John D. (trustee)
  - Roman, Gail H.
  - Romeskie, Martha
  - Ronch, Judah
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Roosevelt, Frank
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, [2 folders]
  - Rosanoff, Lieff
  - Rose, Robert
  - Rose, William K., [5 folders]
  - Roselli, Bruno
  - Rosen, Ellen Israel
  - Rosen, Fred M.
  - Rosen, Warren A.
  - Rosenberg, Evelyn Kiuy
  - Rosenblatt, Julia Carlson
  - Rosenthal, Melvin
  - Ross, Howard N.
  - Ross, (Miss) James Bruce
  - Ross, Janet (Mrs. Walters)
  - Ross, Ken
  - Ross, Susan Getman
  - Rothwell, William F., Jr., [2 folders]
  - Rourke, Constance M.
  - Rousseas, Stephen W., [2 folders]
  - Rovane, Carol
  - Rovere, Richard
  - Rowley, Jean Brintnall
  - Roy, Linda Margeret
  - Rvark, Margaret Annette
  - Rubenstein, Lewis, [5 folders]
  - Rubino, Michael C.
  - Rubsam, Nancy Quackenbush
  - Rudie, Robert
  - Rudin, Bernard D.
  - Ruff, Willie H., Jr.
  - Ruggles, Nancy Orbison
  - Rumble, Wilfred Jr.
  - Russell, Doria Aurela
  - Russo, Charles
  - Ruud, Paul
  - Ryan, Kevin
  - Ryan, Richard
  - Ryberg, Inez Scott, [2 folders]
  - Ryon, Florence
- S
  - Sa
  - Sc
  - Se
  - Sh
  - Si-Sk
  - Sl-Sm
  - So-Sq
  - Sta-Sti
  - Sto-Str
  - Su-Sz
  - Sachs, Jennifer
  - Sacristan, Dolores
  - Sadowsky, Stephen
  - Sague, Mary Landon, [2 folders]
  - Sahi, Surinder
  - Saini, Krishan G.
  - Salguero, Carol G.
  - Salinas, Soledad
  - Salmon, Lucy Maynard, [14 folders]
  - Salmon, Martha
  - Saltzer, Sam
  - Sandar, Volkmar
  - Sanders, Henry M. (trustee)
  - Sandison, Helen, [2 folders]
  - Sanford, Nevitt
  - Sano, Emily J.
  - Sargent, Elizabeth
  - Sarita, Gregory
  - Sasse, Hannah
  - Sather, Clifford
  - Satz, Arthur
  - Saulis, Stephen
  - Saunders, Catherine
  - Saunders, Frederick Albert
  - Saunders, Judith
  - Saunders, Kenneth J.
  - Saunders, Wayne
  - Savarese, John
  - Savitzkaya, Lydia
  - Saward, David J.
  - Sawyer, Harriet
  - Sayles, Emma
  - Scanlan, John
  - Scaravaglione, Concetta
  - Schachman, Marc
  - Schaffmer, Charles E.
  - Schaffter, Dorothy
  - Schalk, David L.
  - Schalk, Elizabeth B.
  - Scheer, Deborah Satz (Mrs. Justin)
  - Scheer, Sherry Lyn
  - Scheidt, Rick J.
  - Schell, Orville H., Jr. (trustee)
  - Schendinger, Herman
  - Scher, Deborah S.
  - Schnepel, Daisy
  - Schnepel, Marguerite Colie
  - Schorr, Gerald J.
  - Schou, James N.
  - Schroer, Joanna Skaates
  - Schuldermann, Ulrike (Mrs. Peter Rettig)
  - Schumacher, Frederick T.
  - Schwartz, Judith Elkin
  - Schwarz, O. Douglas
  - Schweinitz, Margaret de
  - Schwendinger, Julia R.
  - Scott, Faith (Crandall)
  - Scott, Mary Augusta
  - Scott, Sarah E.
  - Scovil, Georgianna W.
  - Scranton, Robert L.
  - Scult, Melvin
  - Sears, John F.
  - Secundy, Marian Gray
  - Selemon, Alex
  - Seltzer, Lenore Chaltetz
  - Semple, Elen C.
  - Senff, Charles H.
  - Sera, Luigi
  - Serafine, Mary Louise
  - Serra, Vicente
  - Seth, Ramo
  - Setliff, Dorene
  - Setliff, Edson
  - Severo, Richard
  - Severs, Richard
  - Sevrens, Glenn
  - Sewall, Eunice D.
  - Sewell, Elizabeth
  - Seymour, Margaret Jones
  - Shanley, Mary L.
  - Shapiro, Herbert
  - Sharp, J. Stanley
  - Shartin, Daniel C.
  - Shattuck, Charles H.
  - Shattuck, George Burbank
  - Shaw, Eileen
  - Shaw, Dr. Ernest
  - Shaw, Graham K.
  - Shaw, William D., Jr.
  - Shearer, Linda
  - Sheldon, Smith (trustee)
  - Sheridan, Dixie (Massad)
  - Sherman, Drusa Wilker (Mrs. Albert)
  - Sherman, Joan
  - Sherwin, Martha May (Reynolds)
  - Sherwood, Margeret Pollock
  - Sherwood, William R.
  - Shields, David S.
  - Shoemaker, Innis
  - Shultz, Herbert L.
  - Sicar, Majursi Chaki
  - Silver, Kenneth E.
  - Silverberg, Joel S.
  - Simonson, Gregory F.
  - Simpson, Alan, [11 folders]
  - Singer, Brett
  - Singer, Joel David
  - Singh, Sally Hey
  - Sircar, Manjuri Chaki
  - Sirjamabi, John
  - Skinner, William (trustee)
  - Skow, Marilyn
  - Slade, Mrs. Bernard N.
  - Slipper, Louise
  - Smiley, Albert Keith
  - Smiley, Daniel M. (trustee)
  - Smith, Alison A.
  - Smith, Bruce James
  - Smith, Erminnie A.
  - Smith, Frances Alward (trustee)
  - Smith, Gertrude, [2 folders]
  - Smith, Henrietta T. [first full-time black faculty member, see also Sterling Allen Brown]
  - Smith, Jane Prouty (trustee)
  - Smith, Joel
  - Smith, Rev. John E.
  - Smith, John Z., Jr.
  - Smith, Kathryn S.
  - Smith, Lillian
  - Smith, Marc
  - Smith, Margaret A. Pollard
  - Smith, M. Brewster
  - Smith, Marian W.
  - Smith, Martin W.
  - Smith, Mary Carroll
  - Smith, Morgan L. (trustee)
  - Smith, Norman C. (treasurer)
  - Smith, Virginia B., [32 folders]
  - Smith, William Wallace
  - Snowden, Kenneth
  - Snyder, Alice D.
  - Solum, John
  - Southwick, Mildred D.
  - Souza, Eileen
  - Spalding, William L., Jr
  - Sperry, Alice Parker
  - Spicer, Donald Z. and Susan, [2 folders]
  - Spiegel, Richard
  - Spies, Claudio
  - Sprinchorn, Evert M.
  - Stambaugh, Joan
  - Stanford, W. Bedell
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady
  - Starbuck, Kathryn H. (trustee)
  - Stathidis, Despina Garofalls
  - Stavrides, Ria
  - Stearns, Frances Fowler
  - Stearns, Robert
  - Stechow, Wolfgang
  - Steele, Richard E.
  - Steerman, James B.
  - Steinberg, Leo
  - Stemple, Irene S.
  - Stellato, Anthony C.
  - Stephenson, Richard D.
  - Sterling, Emma R.
  - Sterling, George W.
  - Stern, H. Peter (trustee)
  - Stern, Lilo
  - Stevens, Gwendolyn Hamilton
  - Stevens, Norton (trustee)
  - Stevens, Simone
  - Stevenson, Dr. Jean K.
  - Stewart, Edith M.
  - Stewart, Jeannie C.
  - Stewart, Meg
  - Stillman, C. Chauncey (trustee)
  - Stillman, Peter G.
  - Stimson, Barbara
  - Stimson, Dorothy
  - Stokes, G. Allison
  - Stoller, David
  - Stolley, Karen A.
  - Stone, Jeannette Galambos
  - Stone, L. Joseph, [12 folders]
  - Stone, Walter B.
  - Stone, Ruth Perkins
  - Stopher, William
  - Stotlar, Curtis
  - Stout, Lawrence N.
  - Stover, Robert C.
  - Strand, Allen R.
  - Stratton, Julius A. (trustee)
  - Strauss, D. Pieter
  - Streeter, John W.
  - Streit, Margaret Martin
  - Streit, Raymond Samuel
  - Strelsky, Nikander, [4 folders]
  - Striker, Cecil
  - Stroebe, Lilian L., [3 folders]
  - Strong, Augustusttopkins (trustee)
  - Struck, Henriette
  - Sullivan, H. Patrick
  - Suter, Robert B.
  - Suter, Valerie J.
  - Swain, Barbara, [2 folders]
  - Swan, Antoinette
  - Swan, Cyrus
  - Swan, Frances W.
  - Sward, Sven M.
  - Sweeney, Denise V.
  - Sweeney, Michael J.
  - Sweezey, Charles O.
  - Sweezy, Maxine Y.
  - Swenarton, Jane
  - Swift, Charles W.
  - Swift, Susan Forrest
  - Swint, Sheryl
- T
  - Ta
  - Te-Th
  - Ti
  - To-Tz
  - Taaffe, James G.
  - Taft, Frances Prindle (trustee)
  - Tait, Marion
  - Tallon, Andrew
  - Tananbaum, Duane
  - Tappan, Eva March
  - Taub, Michael
  - Tavel, Morton A.
  - Taylor, Bruce
  - Taylor, Jane Bliss
  - Taylor, Katherine (trustee)
  - Taylor, Lily Rose
  - Taylor, Lucy D.
  - Taylor, Nelson E., Jr.
  - Taylor, Robert E. (trustee)
  - Taylor, Ruth
  - Teasdale, Phyllis Davison, [2 folders]
  - Tefft, Thomas Alexander
  - Tenenbaum, Barbara Appell
  - Tenney, Sanborn
  - Terry, Harriet
  - Textor, Lucy E.
  - Thallon - SEE Hill, Ida (Thallon)
  - Thelberg, Elizabeth B.
  - Theophilus, Florence and Victoria
  - Thomas, Donna M.
  - Thomas, Vinod
  - Thompson, Alexander "Sandy" MacKenzie
  - Thompson, Annette
  - Thomas, C. Mildred, [14 folders]
  - Thompson, Edward
  - Thompson, Frederick Ferris, [5 folders]
  - Thompson, John (trustee)
  - Thompson, Mary Clark, [8 folders]
  - Thompson, Mary Thaw
  - Thomson, Vera B., [2 folders]
  - Thornbury, Zita L., [4 folders]
  - Thornley, Isobel D.
  - Thornton, Eileen M.
  - Thornton, Robert H.
  - Thurston, Ada (trustee)
  - Tillman, Frank
  - Tilton, Eleanor M.
  - Timberlake, Ellen M.
  - Timm, Ruth Marie
  - Toegel, Edith
  - Tokay, Elbert (Tokaji), [2 folders]
  - Tomer, John F.
  - Toner, Patrick G.
  - Tongue, Margaret Ann
  - Tonks, Oliver S.
  - Trager, Helen G.
  - Trainor, Freda Strongman
  - Trainor, Roberta "Robin" Wells
  - Trask, Georgianne Sampson
  - Travis, Jeffrey L.
  - Treadwell, Aaron Louis
  - Tremelling, Michael J.
  - Treworgy, Mildred L.
  - Triantaphilides, Catherine
  - Tristram, Phillipa
  - Tsao, Clara Ming-His
  - Tucker, Edward B.
  - Tucker, Martha (Sharpe)
  - Tucker, Rosalie G.
  - Tuggle, Sharon
  - Turbin, Carole
  - Turkenkopf, Iris Jane
  - Turnbull, Colin M.
  - Turner, Susan Jane
- U
  - Underhill, Adelaide, [4 folders]
  - Uribe, Blanca Cecelia
  - Uridge, Margaret Whitney
- V
  - Vacharasiridham, Nantanee
  - Valente, William Edward
  - Vallecillo, Irma
  - Van Ackere, Albert J.
  - Van Ackere, Huguette M.
  - Van Alstine, Helen
  - Van Demark, Richard E. (trustee)
  - Van Den Haag, Ernest
  - Vandercar, Sandra
  - Vanderpool, Hilda E.
  - Vander Veer, Delma D.
  - Vander Veer, Garrett L.
  - Van de Water, Julia Chatterton
  - Van Dusen, Henry P.
  - Van Evera, Mary (Congdon) (trustee)
  - Van Ingen, Henry, [2 folders]
  - Van Norden, Bryan
  - Van Vliet, Benson
  - Van Wagner, Marcia
  - Vassar, Catherine
  - Vassar, James
  - Vassar, John E.
  - Vassar, John Guy, [2 folders]
  - Vassar, Matthew, [60 folders]
  - Vassar (towns), [3 folders]
  - Vassar, Matthew, Jr.
  - Vassar Brothers Institute
  - Vassar Family Genealogy, [2 folders]
  - Veblen, Eric
  - Venable, Ruth Dillard
  - Venable, Vernon
  - Veto, Miklos
  - Vilardi, Teresa Jane
  - Villard, Mary St. John (trustee), [2 folders]
  - Villmoare, Adelaide H.
  - Vincent, Barbara
  - Vincent, Jeffrey S.
  - Vining, Joyce C.
  - Vogel, Lawrence A.
  - Von der Thusen, Joachim
  - Voorhees, Carol G.
  - Vorbiov, Masha N.
  - Vromen, Suzanne
  - Vukanovich, Yelena
- W
  - Wa
  - We
  - Wh
  - Wic-Wil
  - Win-Wiz
  - Wo-Wz
  - Waddell, Dickens
  - Wade, Melvin
  - Waggener, Ellen
  - Waggoner, Margaret Ann
  - Wagner, Anne Middleton
  - Wagoner, Louisa C.
  - Walker, Donna N.
  - Walker, Helen B.
  - Walker, Sydnor
  - Wallace, John E.
  - Wallace, Robert
  - Wallach, John
  - Walsh, George
  - Walter, Jennifer
  - Walters, Mary Jane
  - Waluschka, Katherine
  - Walworth, Reubena Hyde
  - Wann, Lois
  - Ward, Aileen
  - Ward, Susan Page
  - Ware, Caroline F., [2 folders]
  - Ware, Naomi
  - Warren, Janet Christine
  - Warren, Katharine
  - Warthin, Aldred Scott, Jr., [4 folders]
  - Washburn, Margaret Floy, [2 folders]
  - Waterman, Otis T.
  - Waters, Robert S.
  - Watsky, Andrew
  - Weber, Mary Louise
  - Webster, Harold
  - Webster, Helen W.
  - Wedlake, Wendy
  - Weedin, Everett K.
  - Weeks, Carnes, Dr.
  - Weeks, Rosann M.
  - Wehrle, John J.
  - Weigt, Claire I.
  - Weil, Nicole
  - Weinberg, David
  - Weingarten, Nina
  - Weingartner, Rudolph H.
  - Weinrich, Carl
  - Weisenfeld, Judith
  - Weisberger, Bernard A.
  - Weisenfeld, Judith
  - Weiss, Sydna S.
  - Weitz, Morris
  - Welch, George T.
  - Welles, Elizabeth
  - Wells, Barbara J., [2 folders]
  - Wells, Emilie Louise
  - Wells, Mary Evelyn
  - Wertheimer, Jack
  - Wessells, Michael
  - West, Suzanne E.
  - Westcott, Malcolm R., [2 folders]
  - Weston, Anthony E.
  - Weston, Lydia
  - Wheeler, Harry A. (trustee)
  - Wheeler, Helen Pendleton, [2 folders]
  - Wheeler, Isabel
  - Wheeler, Jessie F.
  - Wheeler, Mary
  - Wheeler, Ruth
  - Whiffen, Marcus
  - Whipple, Taggart (trustee)
  - White, Elizabeth M.
  - White, Florence Donnell
  - White, Henry Seely, [2 folders]
  - White, Paula K.
  - White, Thomas
  - Whitney, Lois
  - Whitney, Marian P.
  - Whitney, Mary W.
  - Wick, Frances Gertrude
  - Wiebe, Edward
  - Wieder, Luzie
  - Wight, Rezin A. (trustee)
  - Wilder, Susanna
  - Wilkie, John
  - Wilkins, Ann Thomas
  - Wilkinson, Martha Wyman
  - Willard, Nancy
  - Willey, Richard J.
  - Williams, Barbara Ruth
  - Williams, Brad Gerred
  - Williams, Donald B.
  - Williams, Elizabeth (Stillman) (trustee)
  - Williams, Esther L.
  - Williams, Hermine Weigel
  - Williams, Mary A.
  - Williamson, George, Jr.
  - Willis, Frances Elizabeth
  - Willison, Malcolm R.
  - Wilson, Carol
  - Wilson, Hugh
  - Wilson, Richard, [3 folders]
  - Wilson, William D.
  - Wing, Marion
  - Winslow, Mrs. Paul T.
  - Wise, Jacqueline G.
  - Wishard, Audrey
  - Wislocki, Florence Clothier, [2 folders]
  - Wittig, Monique
  - Wittner, Lawrence S.
  - Wohl, Anthony S.
  - Wolf, Diana
  - Wolff, Werner
  - Wolfson, Eugenia Walden
  - Wolin, Helga D.
  - Wolkonsky, Catherine
  - Wood, Elizabeth
  - Wood, Frances A., [2 folders]
  - Wood, Frederic C., Jr., [8 folders]
  - Wood, J. A.
  - Wood, Mary Lee (Hutchins)
  - Wood, Nathan E.
  - Wood, Willis D.
  - Woodruff, Edith S.
  - Woodward, Douglas P.
  - Woodwell, Margot (Bell)
  - Work, Galen R. Jr.
  - Wriggins, W. Howard
  - Wright, Margaret R.
  - Wylie, Diana
  - Wylie, Laura J.
- Y
  - Yarmosky, Amy Bard
  - Yavelow, Jonathan
  - Yellow Robe, Evelyn
  - Yoder, Jay
  - Yoder, William R.
  - Yost, Mary
  - Young, Anne G.
  - Young, Newell H.
  - Young, Partricia Arlene
- Z
  - Zagorin, Perez
  - Zeraffa, Michel
  - Zern, David S.
  - Zlotowski, Ignace
  - Zoli, Mary Janet
  - Zorb, Elizabeth
  - Zorzoli, Anita
  - Zoupanos, Theodore S.
  - Zucker, Diane
  - Zuckerman, David C.
  - Zuckerman, Diana M.
  - Zuckerman, Israel